(Sheldon:)Be part of that proud tradition.
(Leonard:)I'll go get Penny while that guy
spits on our food.
(Raj:)Do you think they gave Wolverine
an adamantium prostate?
(Howard:)That's a stupid question.
(Raj:)We're having
a conversation about
(Raj:)probing the heinies
of superheroes.
(Raj:)There are no stupid questions.
(Man:)Yes?
(Leonard:)Oh, um, is
Penny here?
(Man:)You're Leonard, right?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Man:)Damn, it's good
to finally meet you, son.
(Leonard:)Okay, I think a bit of
context here might help.
(Penny:)Oh, hey, Leonard.
I see you met my dad.
(Leonard:)Oh, good.
(Leonard:)Context.
(Penny's Dad:)Come on in, buddy.
(Penny's Dad:)Take a load off.
(Penny:)Oh, gee, Dad,
Leonard can't stay.
(Penny:)He just dropped by to say hello.
(Penny:)Thanks for stopping by, sweetie.
(Penny:)I'll see you later.
(Penny:)Bye.
(Leonard:)That was odd.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪